JASON DELIA

UX Engineer



I am an experienced web developer with more than 10 years in the industry. I understand the importance of adhering to web standards and believe that code and design are equally important and should work together to create visually exciting and functional apps and websites.

EXPERIENCE

Senior UX Engineer March 2010 - Present

Thomson Reuters

Building product prototypes and assisting development teams in implementation. Working with product owners to conceptualize new products and features through interaction and visual design.

Senior Web Developer June 2005 - March 2010

Thomson Reuters

Front-end web developer working on an ASP.NET code base. Building master pages and reusable controls. Working in the middle tier and database when necessary.

Site Developer June 2004 - June 2005

Thomson Financial

Producer, Webcasting Services 2002 - June 2004

Thomson Financial

EDUCATION

Masters in Business Administration: Concentration in Project Management

2008

New York Institute of Technology

Summa Cum Laude

Delta Mu Delta International Honor Society in Business Administration Candidate

B.S. in Business Administration: Concentration in Management Information Systems

2002

Seton Hall University

Magna Cum Laude



AJAX ASP.NET CSS3 Fireworks Git HTML5 IXD JQuery Javascript JSON Photoshop PHP RWD SQL SVN Web Standards Visual Design XSLT

CONTACT

jasonadelia@gmail.com 631.949.5979

WORK SAMPLES

Samples of work available upon request.

View latest CSS experiments on codepen (http://codepen.io/jasonadelia).

View this resume in a web browser for the fully responsive experience (http://jasonadelia.github.com)